this world is not yet ready for all that
you will do
your time will come diana
and everything will be different
citizens of the world
i'm here to change your life
anything you want
[Music]
anything you dream of you can have it
look like you saw a ghost
diana lucky you it's like not one day
has passed
i don't want to be like anyone i want to
be an
apex predator
you've always had everything while
people like me have had nothing
well now it's my turn
get used to it
i've never been one for rules the answer
is always
more
the way i fly they will never find us i
forgot to tell you
what radar will they will they shoot at
[Applause]
[Music]
us
barbara what did you do
you know i'm not so keen on this one i
figure uh you are but
you know what i'm ready to go i think we
can do better
parachute pants yeah um does everybody
parachute now